

## CONTACT ME AT

amrmoussa2016@icloud.com

https://github.com/Amrmoussa777

AmrMoussa.github.io

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/a

00201067865284

Cairo,EG

## SKILLS SUMMARY

- Expert knowledge of Swift, UIKit and Core Data.
- Strong object-oriented design, programming and debugging skills
- Expert with Back handling using RestulAPI and Alamofire
- strong knowledge with design patterns MVC,MVVM and SOLID
- Expert knowledge of Swift, UIKit and Core Data.
- good knowledge with Nodejs
- expert with versioning using Git
- proven strong teaching and communication skills

#### LANGUAGES

swift

Node.IS

- good knowledge with Nodejs
- good knowledge with Nodejs

# **AMR MOUSSA**

## SOFTWARE ENGINEER

### PERSONAL PROFILE

Experienced software engineer with a passion for developing innovative applications that helps for better life . Ability to write clean code to create systems that are reliable and user-friendly. they said "the best way to master something is to teach it " so i a have the skills to present and deliver information in a fast and understandable way equiped with teaching experience .

## WORK EXPERIENCE

## Teaching assistant

Armed Forces Technical Institute | Sep 2019 - present

- Designed and taught a well tailored computer science course for senior level.
- Engaged with students with technical problems enhanced their grades.
- Assessed student with oral and essay exams.

# IOS Developer

freelancer | Aug 2018 - present

 Design and code innovative mobile application for IOS, macOS and watchOS.

#### **EDUCATIONAL HISTORY**

computer and information systems Mansoura University
Bachelor in software engineering | Oct 2014 - Jun 2018

- GPA: 2.79
- Courses involved problem solving and programming content.
- Courses were augmented with economics and managerial content.

## **PROJECTS**

### iPay

UI,UX - IOS developer Mar 2020

- using Swift and RealmDB for data persistence.
- [github] https://github.com/Amrmoussa777/iPay

### iConnect

IOS developer May 2020

- swift 5
- Firebase DB for data persistence
- Firebase storage for Media persistence.
- [github] https://github.com/Amrmoussa777/iconnect